本字幕由Nicolas Bourbaki调轴及合并双语 首先发布于SubHD
转载请注明来源保留信息 开源分享的互联网精神你有我有大家有
Nicolas Bourbaki不建议也不对任何利用本字幕生成的视频负责
等等，我们之后会放回来吗？
Wait, are we gonna put it back when we're done with it?
欢迎大家到我们的仓库协助改错：https://github.com/N-Bourbaki/Rick-and-Morty-Chinese-Subtitles
为什么？ 只有秘密藏宝图有价值
Why? The only thing of value on it is the secret treasure map.
其他只是治理国家的指示
The rest is just instructions for running a country.
－网络上应该有　－感觉不太好
- and I'm pretty sure they're online. - It just feels a little wrong.
莫蒂，你是要当个他妈的美式乖乖
Morty, are you gonna be a fuckin' America nerd
还是要跟外公一起偷《宪法》？
or are you gonna be cool and steal the Constitution with Grandpa?
《美国宪法》
帮我拿着，我来打开这个密封柜
Here, hold this while I crack the hermetic seal.
干吗不用这个就好？
Why not just use this again?
莫蒂，你把藏宝图毁了
Morty! You just destroyed the map
还启动了自由女神里的巨人刺客
and activated the giant assassin hidden in the Statue of Liberty!
抱歉，等等，什么？
I'm sorry! Wait, what?
自由女神是特洛伊木马，莫蒂
It was a Trojan horse, Morty.
法国人不可信
Never trust the French.
好，我们玩够了，联邦政府一定会很生气，做得好
All right. Fun's fun, but the federal government's gonna be pissed again. Way to go.
今天还是美国的生日
And on America's birthday
我也不确定感恩节是什么日子
or whatever the fuck Thanksgiving is.
瑞克和莫蒂，你们被逮捕了
Rick and Morty, you are under arrest
你们已经被防传送光包围了
and surrounded by an anti-portal shimmer!
快出来，双手举高
Come out with your hands up!
祝我感恩节快乐
Well, happy Thanksgiving to me!
不知道那道光
Can't wait to see what a shimmer
对我的前列腺会有什么影响
does to my prostate.
爸，你能快点搞定这件事吗？
Dad, can you please just end whatever this is?
我能理解你很生气，总统
I understand you're upset, Mr. President
其实全是莫蒂的错
it's honestly all Morty's fault.
但请你叫莫名穿着迷彩装的童军
But in the meantime, you really want to keep your army
离开我家的前院
of pointlessly camouflaged eagle scouts off my lawn.
少对我发号施令，你这反美人渣，你这恐怖分子
Don't tell me what I want you anti-American piece of shit! You terrorist!
你把这词滥用到没意义了，总统
You know, you use that word so much it's lost all meaning, Mr. P.
恐怖分子现在代表什么意义？
It's like, at this point, what's a terrorist?
就只是你不喜欢的人而已
It's a guy you don't like, big deal.
我就叫你的手下别过来了
Told you to stand down.
你就这样失去了两名英勇的士兵
You just lost two soldiers over here. Good men.
或许你自己才是恐怖分子
Might be time to look at the terrorist in the mirror.
你想开战吗？
You want a war?
我会把你这太空人关进幻影地带
I'll put your outer space ass in a goddamn phantom zone
在你的脖子上绑氪星石
with a bar of kryptonite soap around your neck.
你完蛋了，山查兹，听到没有？
You're done, Sanchez! You hear me?
他这次很生气
He's really pissed this time.
你们两个不如就直接开干吧？
Why don't you guys just fuck and get it over with?
谢谢，桑美，但我有更好的办法
OK, well thank you Summer, but I think I've got a better option.
－爸，不行　－我别无他法
- Dad, no. - Hands are tied, sweetie.
我得把自己变成火鸡
I have to turn myself into a turkey and trick the President
骗总统赦免我
into giving me a presidential turkey pardon.
又来？ 你这招用过几次了？
Again? How many times have you done this?
我不知道，杰瑞，我住几年了？
I don't know, Jerry, how many years have I lived here?
回答时注意一点
Careful how you answer that.
天啊，瑞克，你常常用这招
Jeez, Rick. You know, you've done this a lot.
总统难道不会料到吗？
Don't you think the President might see it coming this time?
他或许会，莫蒂，我都想好了
He probably will, Morty. That's all part of the dance.
我曾在典礼前洗脑火鸡驯养人
In the past, I've inserted myself into the potential turkey pardonee population
潜入候选赦免火鸡群中
by brainwashing the presidential turkey wrangler prior to the ceremony.
但那火鸡驯养人已经被安乐死了
But this time, the turkey wrangler's been euthanized
火鸡会使用装甲军用车辆运送
and the turkeys will be transported by armored military vehicles.
但车是我控制的空壳公司生产的
Vehicles manufactured by ghost corporations that I control.
我们审查过了
Which we have audited.
－所以我能进入…　－中央电脑
- Allowing me access to... - Central computers.
－追踪…　－真正的装甲车
- To track the... - Real armored transports,
－他绝对…　－能追踪并偷上车
- which he can never... - Totally track and sneak aboard.
就算他跑上车了
And even if he does he'll be on a truck
车上有很多火鸡和武装陆战队员
full of turkeys and fully armed marines...,
他们认不出我
Who won't recognize me
因为人眼无法辨认不同火鸡
because the human eye is inherently face blind to turkeys.
那些陆战队员的眼睛不会是人眼
Fortunately, those marines won't have human eyes.
会是火鸡眼
They'll have turkey eyes.
天啊，你们不如直接开干吧？
Jesus ever-loving Christ. Why don't you two just fuck and get it over with?
小心点，杜万，你能当副总统
Careful, Dwayne. You're only vice-president
是因为我需要一成的白人票
because I need 10% of the white vote.
有个法国巨人刺客正在攻击纽约
There's a giant French assassin attacking New York
你竟然在用战情室
and you're using the war room
跟你的酒鬼科幻男友比大小？
to measure dicks with your alcoholic sci-fi boyfriend.
瑞克山查兹比蒸气驱动的
Rick Sanchez is more dangerous
那个法国婊子危险多了
than some steam-powered French bitch
纽约可以自己解决危机
and New York can handle its own global emergencies.
上将？展开深啼行动
General! Initiate Operation Deep Gobble.
库普，今天是感恩节
Coop, not on Thanksgiving.
我必须出征，玛莉露
It's what I trained for, Mary Lou.
－这不关我们的事　－宝贝
- It ain't our fight. - Baby.
你希望肚子里的小赛车手
That little race car driver you got bakin' in your belly.
在什么样的世界长大？
What world do you want him rearin' up in?
穿实验衣的尖头发神秘博士
One where some spiky-haired Doctor Who in a lab coat
可以改变天空颜色的世界吗？
can change the color of the sky?
还是你想让他能开皮卡车载热狗
Or a world where he can fill his pick-up with hot dogs and drive it
给喜欢这种音乐类型的人吃？
to a jukebox full of our demographic's current favorite music?
当然是后者，但…
Obviously the latter, but...
既然这样，玛莉露
Well, that world, Mary Lou,
如果想要有热狗、卡车
the one with those meals, vehicles
和附近的人爱听的歌
and songs people in this 30-mile area prefer...
我们就要当正派的人
that world needs a few good men,
去国防部的秘密实验室变成火鸡
in a secret Pentagon lab turning into turkeys.
你拔完羽毛再回来，库普
You come back without feathers, Coop.
天啊，我好爱这个国家
God, I love this country.
奶油农场
*怀着宝宝的女孩儿，开着皮卡的我*
*I got a pregnant girl and a pickup truck*
*我选择了女孩儿，而皮卡选择了我*
*I got one by choice and the other by luck*
*是时候变成火鸡了*
*But now it's time to turn into a turkey*
*惟愿有朝一日世界和平*
*I hope there can be peace one day*
*到了功成之日，请为我的DNA祈祷*
*Till then, I pray my DNA*
*让我变回自己*
*Gets backed up*
基因备份完成
这药丸里有追踪晶片
These pills contain tracking chips
可以辨别你们的身份
that identify each of you as individuals.
这之后会很重要
That will be important later.
*咯咯，咯咯*
*Gobble, gobble*
*咕咕，咕咕*
*当我变成火鸡*
*When I turn into a turkey*
汉德森火鸡牧场
好，各位，检查每一只火鸡
All right, boys, search every bird.
如果发现山查兹，就啼个几声
If Sanchez is here, I wanna hear you gobblin'.
让我仔细看看，混蛋
Let me look at you, scum!
你走吧，火鸡
Get outta here, you wobbleneck!
中士，这跟模拟的时候不一样
Sarge, this... this ain't like the simulation, man.
－我不喜欢　－振作点，马丁纳
- I don't like it. - Keep it together, Martinez!
我们已经到现场了
Eyes are on the ground, sir.
－没发现爱因斯坦　－提高警觉
- No sign of Einstein. - Stay frosty, gentlemen.
一定要好好守住这群火鸡
I want this pardoning pipeline airtight.
总统，我们把车库门破解打开了
Sir! We have hacked the garage door. We are in.
－目标就在眼前　－那是机器人
- Eyes on the bogey. - Or you've got eyes on a robot.
恕我直言，我分得出人肉和机器
All due respect, sir, I know flesh when I see it.
人肉机器人应该能争取一点时间
Those flesh-covered robots should buy us some time.
候选火鸡应该就在这辆车上
The pardonable turkeys should be on that truck.
开启隐形功能
Ship, go stealth.
汤米火鸡运输
罗德、芬奇，去看看
Rodriguez, Fincher! Get eyes on that!
火鸡海军陆战队员
Turkey marines.
总统是来真的
The President came to play.
－干扰无线电　－收到
- Jam those two radios. - Confirmed.
天啊
Jeez!
芬奇、罗德，快回答
Fincher, Rodriguez, come in!
收到，队长，没有异状
Copy, copy, tango, all good.
只是树枝掉到车顶上而已
Just a couple of branches on the roof.
不准关掉无线电
Don't ever turn your radio off again!
－我们不投降　－我们绝不投降
- We will not surrender! - We will never surrender!
－我们不投降　－是吗？
- We will not surrender! - Oh, yeah?
把大卫布莱恩箱拿来
Bring in the David Blaine box.
天啊，是大卫布莱恩箱吗？
Damn, is that a David Blaine box?
我就说吧，应该要去我爸妈家的
I told you, we should have just gone to my parents' house.
－你没说　－我没说出口
- No, you didn't. - Well, I didn't say it out loud.
但大家都知道我想去那里
But it should be well known by now that I'd always rather be there.
－天啊，不　－天啊，瑞克
- Oh, God! Oh, no! - Jeez, Rick!
总统，我们把瑞克和莫蒂关住了
Sir, we've got Rick and Morty inside the box.
－那就证实了　－什么？
- Then that confirms it. - Sir?
大卫布莱恩箱关不住瑞克山查兹
No David Blaine box could hold Rick Sanchez.
扫描火鸡车
Scan the turkey truck.
怪了，芬奇和罗德的晶片有异状
That's weird. ID chips for Fincher and Rodriguez are glitching.
山查兹
Sanchez.
我会亲自对付那混蛋
I'll deal with this bastard myself.
总统，别逞强，死了就无法连任
Sir, don't be a cowboy. You can't get re-elected dead.
系统已校准，总统
System's calibrated, sir.
这药丸里有追踪晶…
That pill contains a tracking chip that will identify...
我知道，之后会很重要
I know, it'll be important later.
来吧
Do it!
总统稍后就会赦免火鸡
Moments from now, the President will be pardoning a turkey.
火鸡选择区
我们快成功了，莫蒂，那废物要准时现身了
Home stretch, Morty. Here comes dipshit right on schedule.
一定不会出错
Nothing can go wrong now.
－我的天啊，那是…　－靠
- Jesus! Is that... - Oh, shit.
总统占上风了，外公搞砸了
The President has the upper hand. Grandpa fucked up.
戴上墨镜，快装成火鸡
Sunglasses on! Act like a turkey!
－什么？你会怕？　－装成火鸡
- What? Are you scared? - Act like a turkey!
这两位是罗德和芬奇，总统
That's Rodriguez and Fincher, sir.
是瑞克和莫蒂，他妈没用的废物
It's Rick and Morty, you useless fucking stump humper!
抱歉，别跟你一成的朋友说此事
Sorry, don't tell 10% of your friends I called you that.
－总统　－山查兹，你就认输吧
- Mr. President. - Sanchez, admit it. You lose.
你只要认输，我就放过你
Say it and I'll let your loser ass go.
你没唾液腺还想吐我口水？
Did you just try to spit in my face with no saliva gland?
快赦免我，混蛋
Just pardon me, dick!
－为什么？　－因为呢
- Why the hell would I? - Oh, I don't know.
我若搬去加拿大，就会赢过美国
'Cause if I move to Canada, they'll be the best country.
我要啄瞎你
I'll peck your goddamn eyes out!
－嘿　－靠，我的羽毛
- Ouch! Hey! - Shit! My plume!
嘿，后退
Back off!
蓝莓，蓝莓掉到地上了
Blueberries! We got blueberries down!
稳住阵脚，火鸡正在疯狂觅食
Hold your positions. It's a feeding frenzy!
我看不到，我能看到270度
I can't see. I mean, I can see... 270 degrees.
这角度太广了
It's too many degrees!
长官，我们的心理战快输了
Sir, we are losing the mental game down here.
振作点，各位，总统还在里面
Keep it together, soldier! POTUS is still in that pen!
纽约被法国夺走了
We just lost New York to France!
马上把总统抓出来
Pull out the President right now!
队长，把总统抓出来
Gobble Tango, I want POTUS out of that pen!
这是命令，扫描总统晶片
That's an order! Locate the President's chip!
收到…
Roger-roger.
他在那里，我找到他了
There he is, I got him.
我们出发，把总统护送出去
Let's go, boys! Let's fly out the Eagle!
嘿，那不是我
Hey, that's not me.
找到总统了，带我们离开
Package is secure. Pull us out.
重新注入基因
Reinjecting subject DNA.
我的天啊，你看起来还真恶心
Hoppin' Jehovah, you look like five pounds of shit in a whore's lunchbox.
你还好吗，总统先生？
You all right, Mr. President?
对，我是总统
Yes. I am the President.
把他清干净，带他到战情室
Clean his ass up and get him to the war room.
火鸡队，你们搞错人了，笨蛋
Hey! Gobble Squad! You got the wrong guy, you morons!
这只蠢火鸡一直乱叫
Look at this dumb piece of shit. Gobbling away.
滚回去
Get back in there!
好，你们都听到副总统的命令了
All right, boys, you heard the VP.
赦免典礼取消了，马上撤退
Pardon is tits up. Pack up and ship out!
至于你呢，山查兹，请慢用
As for you, Sanchez, bon appétit.
这电梯会通往哪里？
Where is this elevator going?
没获选的火鸡都会被送往喂食室
Where all the unchosen turkeys go. The feeding chamber.
这什么鬼东西？
What the fuck is that?
不是东西，是人
Not what... who.
你们唯一该惧怕的就是我
The only thing to fear is... me!
白宫他妈为什么会有小罗斯福的复制蜘蛛？
How the fuck does the White House have a cloned spider of FDR?
那是小罗斯福本人
It's no clone, it's FDR.
他参与了小儿麻痹疫苗实验
He was a guinea pig for the polio vaccine.
我们想知道哪种动物最常行走？
We asked ourselves what walks the most?
“我们”？ 你把自己也算进去？
We? You're taking credit for this?
当总统就得承担包袱，莫蒂
The office comes with baggage, Morty.
－瑞克，我怕死　－别怕，莫蒂
- Rick, I'm afraid to die! - You won't have to be for long, Morty.
我们马上就会变回人类了
We're due to return to human form any second.
－然后呢？　－然后就想办法
- Then what? - Then we just have to
别被蜘蛛吃掉
not get eaten by the spider.
所以我还是要怕死？
Oh, so in other words, be afraid to die?
莫蒂，你如果真的这么爱辩
Morty, if winning an argument is that important to you
那你从来没有活过
you were never alive.
我们来谈条件，杀人
Time for a new deal. Murder!
我受够大家对你的崇拜了
I'm sick of hearing how iconic you were!
等你在脸书出现后
Try having an historical administration
还能受大家喜爱再说吧，死老头
after Facebook goes online, you old-timey bitch!
莫蒂，把面板打开
Morty, tear open that panel!
我们来场炉边谈话，好吗？
How's this for a fireside chat?
－你杀了小罗斯福　－他是怪兽
- You just killed FDR. - He was a monster though.
别把他神话了，他是政治人物
Don't mythologize him, he was a politician.
说到这个，你救了我们一命
Speaking of, you kinda saved our bacon there
所以我愿意跟你谈条件
so I'll make you a deal.
你赦免我，我就把你变回人类
You pardon us and I'll make you human.
－是这只　－人眼真的无法辨识
- Wrong turkey. - Man, the face blindness is real.
帮我把这些人变回人类
I'd like these men turned back into humans, please.
没问题，总统
Yes, of course, Mr. President.
但我们应该已经把所有陆战队员变回人类了
But I thought we already rehumanized all the turkified marines.
把这些人变回人类，我是总统
I'd like these men turned back into humans. I am the President.
遵命，总统，没问题
Yes, sir. Sure thing.
把他们的力量增加十倍
Increase their strength by 1,000%.
那他们就不会是人类了
But... that wouldn't be human.
火鸡一向都比人类优秀
Turkeys have always been more than human.
好吧，你这样我会怀疑…
OK, so right there, now I'm starting to...
我要把纽约卖给法国
I am selling New York to France.
把卖得的钱交给国会
And giving all of the money to Congress.
好耶
All right, yeah!
－这样就对了　－这才是真总统
- Now that's how you do it. - He became President today.
对，尽管议论吧
That's right, murmur.
忙完拿裤子来给我
And when you're done, get me some pants.
如果你是总统
If you're the President
那过去这三个小时
who the hell have we been governing the country with
治理我们国家的人是谁？
for the last three hours?
是冒牌货，笨蛋，你抓错火鸡了
An impostor, you good-for-nothing idiot! You humanized the wrong turkey!
确实有可能，我们不能冒险
It's possible. We shouldn't leave anything to chance.
不能让国会跟错误的总统合作
Wouldn't want Congress working with the wrong President.
有道理，总统先生
A very good point, Mr. President.
我们认为这位爱好合作的先生
Do we believe this fine-feathered, collaborative gentleman
是我们的总司令吗？
to be our commander in chief?
还是我们要让不允许圣诞派对
Or are we gonna let Mr. Cash Bar
免费供酒的人继续当总统？
at the Christmas party stay in office?
支持火鸡总统的人有多少？
All in favor of Turkey President?
荒谬，你觉得他在乎美国吗？
You can't be serious. You think he cares about America?
那你为什么会遇到这种事？
Is that why this is happening to you?
是因为你在乎美国吗？
Because you cared about America?
守卫，这三位是，那叫什么？
Guards, these men are... what is the word?
恐怖分子
Terrorists.
我不管了，启动山查兹雷射拳
OK, screw this. Go, go, Sanchez laser fists!
靠，我刚刚变成了火鸡，对吧？
When I turn into a turkey. Oh, shit. I was a turkey for a while, wasn't I?
好吧，你力气好大
OK, guy's pretty strong.
玛丽陶德林肯
Mary Todd Lincoln!
现在谁才是拖油瓶，婊子？
Who's dead weight now, bitch?
你的屁股马上就会恢复知觉了
You should regain feeling in your ass in a minute.
抱歉，我的炮塔炸掉了你的机车
Sorry my turrets blew up your motorcycle.
快拿衣服给我穿
Just give me some goddamn clothes.
你只能来我家避难，一定很难受
Must suck to have your only safe haven be my house.
你想穿你平常的衣服
You want your regular outfit
还是恐怖分子的衣服？
or should we dress you like a terrorist?
我也能离开，而且我依然是总统
I don't need to be here and I'm still the President.
太好了，那你就赦免我吧
Oh, glad to hear it. That means you can give me that pardon.
不然我就把你赶出去
Or I could put you out with the trash.
你有什么毛病？ 你为什么讨厌这个国家？
What is your problem? Why do you hate this country?
我讨厌全宇宙的每个国家，兄弟
I hate every country in the universe, brother.
国家只是政治人物发明出来发钱给自己的东西而已
They're job placement programs for the politicians that invent them.
好吧，神经病
OK, Fight Club.
我的职责是要保护坐在场边的你
I get paid to protect the sidelines you sit on!
你的职责只是耍嘴皮子
You get paid to make sports metaphors!
我会帮你清砂盆
I clean your litterbox.
让你这自以为酷的书呆子拉屎时
So your little nerd paws don't have to touch another nerd's nerdy poopies
手不会碰到其他书呆子的大便
while you're flexing your grody little edge-lord anus all over it!
大家，或许你们都对也都错
Guys, maybe you're both right and both wrong.
－闭嘴，莫蒂　－闭嘴，莫蒂
- Shut up, Morty! - Shut up, Morty!
你这小贱货，你毁了《宪法》
You little bitch. You destroyed the Constitution.
你才是最可恶的混蛋
You're the biggest booger eater here!
你不能这样对我儿子说话
Do not talk to my son that way.
抱歉，史密斯太太
Sorry, Mrs. Smith.
你们两个联手毁了感恩节
The two of you are ruining Thanksgiving. Together.
快来跟我的家人一起吃饭
And you can both either come to the table and eat food with my family
否则就滚到酒吧去继续吵
or you can keep doing what you're doing at the corner bar.
感恩节上酒吧很可悲
Bars actually suck at Thanksgiving.
我还是搞不太懂
I'm still trying to sort through this.
你们其中一个人希望自己有勇气
One of you wishes you had the personal quality known as courage
另外两个人则想要重要器官？
but the other two of you want actual vital organs?
查理考夫曼翻拍的《绿野仙踪》
This Charlie Kaufman reboot of Wizard Of Oz
简直是场灾难
is destroying itself.
所以我需要大脑，我写得好烂
That's why I need a brain! I'm doing a terrible job writing this!
能把马铃薯递给我吗？
Pass the potatoes?
谢谢
Thank you.
四季豆很好吃，妈
Good green beans, Mom.
火鸡是生的，爸，根本不能吃
The turkey's raw, Dad. Shit's potato bunz.
抱歉，桑美，我们被国家关在光罩里
Sorry, Summer. The United States enclosed us in a shimmer bubble
扰乱了我的烤箱计时器
that scrambled my oven timer.
看来我们真的选错人了
So, I guess elections do have consequences.
吃屎吧，杰瑞，我查过你的资料
Eat my ass, Jerry. I've seen your IRS records.
等你有应税所得再来怪我
You can blame me once you have taxable income.
没错，我也认同杰瑞是废物
Yes, Jerry is a piece of shit. I agree.
各位，那是怎么回事？
Guys? What's that?
宝拉，克提斯总统施行了
Paula, as you can see President Curtis has enacted a plan
把全美火鸡变成超级士兵的计划
to turn all turkeys in America into hybrid super soldiers.
国会在六小时内加薪三次后
The move has 100% approval from Congress
就全体同意通过本法案
following its third pay raise in six hours.
镜头交还给主播
Back to you.
天啊，那混蛋疯了
My god, the bastard's unhinged!
特区会连一只鸟都不剩
There won't be a single bird left in DC!
天啊，在感恩节屠杀原住民？
Oh, wow, wiping out a native population on Thanksgiving?
－这还是第一次　－你说什么？
- That's never happened before. - What did you just say?
我把感恩节跟种族屠杀做了连结
Well, I associated Thanksgiving with genocide.
年轻人都会这样，我不是想…
It's what young people do, I wasn't trying to...
新世界地穴
The Crypt of the New World!
这是我们唯一能扭转乾坤的机会
That could be our one chance to turn this thing around!
你知道地穴的事？
You know about the Crypt?
那宝藏一定被拿光了
So the treasure's already gone.
这就是你偷《宪法》的原因吗？蠢老头子
Wait, is that why you were stealing the Constitution? You old fart dick.
新世界地穴里的不是宝藏
The Crypt of the New World isn't a treasure.
但或许是我们唯一的希望，来吧
But it might be our only hope. Come on.
那个地穴不是在特区吗？
But isn't the Crypt underneath DC?
火鸡总统有军队，陆军军队
The Turkey President's got an army. An actual army!
－还有空军、海军　－讲慢一点
- And an air force! And marines! - Slow down, Morty!
把所有军队都讲一遍
Walk us through every military service.
谁有笔？
Does somebody have a pen?
我们有比任何军队都强大的东西
We've got something more powerful than every army in the world.
其实没有，但只要演讲成功
Well, no, we don't, but with the right speech
就能说服几位受过训练的乡巴佬
we could get a handful of well-trained hillbillies.
我们曾这样对抗过英国，我支持
It worked against the British. I'm in.
用火鸡取代人
Birds replacin' people.
强尼凯许或戴尔恩哈特会怎说？
What would Johnny Cash or Dale Earnhardt say?
他会说，该付诸行动了
He'd say it's time to walk the line
或是开快车经过
or drive very fast between two of them.
我们不接待你这种人
We don't serve your kind here.
天啊，有没有搞错？
Oh my god, are you serious?
自己看
Read the sign.
总统免进 已赊53刀
他是我长官，马文
He's my boss, Marvin.
没事，不信任总统是爱国的表现
It's OK. Mistrusting presidents is a patriotic duty.
电视上那个人不是我
And that guy on TV isn't me.
是一只注入我基因的火鸡
He's a turkey infused with my DNA.
我的天啊
I'll be damned.
我歧视黑人
Well. I'm racist.
别想再带走我的男人了
You better not be here to take my man again.
－玛莉露　－我很穷又怀了孕
- Mary Lou... - I'm poor! And pregnant!
我的宝宝也很穷
With a poor person!
我需要你，还有你宝宝的一成
And I need you. And 10% of your baby.
听着，我知道演讲是不够的
Now look, I know it's going to take more than some speech.
但演讲是什么？不就是问题吗？
But what is a speech? Isn't it just a question?
这句不也是问题吗？演讲是词语
And isn't that a question too? Speeches are words.
重复的词语，条列的词语
Repeated words. Listed words.
重复条列的重复词语，这不重要
Repeated lists of repeated words. None of that matters.
你知道什么最重要吗？
You know what does matter?
我要问你们
Me asking you...
你们愿意照我的话做吗？
will you do what I say?
我只有两个问题
Just two questions, Chief.
没？问题？
Lock? And load?
这其实不是问题，没问题
They're rhetorical, sir. Lock and load!
没问题
Lock and load!
总统，看起来瑞克和莫蒂驾驶着
Sir, we've got Rick and Morty coming in
未授权的星球大战全地域装甲运输走兽
what appears to be an unlicensed Star Wars AT-AT.
现在的年轻人都说是装运走兽
Or as the millennials say, A-T, A-T.
开始了
So it begins.
各位火鸡，我们今晚要奋力反抗
Gobblers! Tonight, we rise!
哦，天啊
Oh, jeez...
驾驶技术不错，山查兹
Nice driving, Sanchez.
护网失效，前方安全
Wire's down, pen is clear.
你们都知道规矩
You know the goddamn rules.
如果看到火鸡，就开枪轰掉
If you see something clucking or pecking put a buckshot in its panties.
天啊，强森死了
Jesus Christ! They got Johnson!
他死得算痛快
He got off easy.
拖住这些混蛋
Hold off the bastards!
－怎么办，瑞克？　－加强火力
- What now, Rick? - Time to turn up the broiler.
这里是…
Is that...
新世界地穴
The Crypt of the New World.
你们在找的宝藏
The treasure you were after
就是美国最古老的秘密
is this country's oldest secret.
被感恩节故事掩盖了好几世纪
One disguised by centuries of Thanksgiving folklore.
这是火鸡恐龙吗？
Is that... a turkey dinosaur?
美国原本的统治者
America's original rulers.
残忍的野兽，猎食懦弱的人类
Merciless beasts, grazing on the flesh of cowering humans.
15世纪时，有艘船坠地了
Then in the 15th century, a vessel crashed.
其实是两艘船，载着我们的救星
Two vessels, really. Onboard, our saviors.
山查兹，跟我同时拉控制杆
Sanchez, pull that lever the same time I do.
靠，他们要打起来了
Oh, shit, they're gonna fight!
不对，等等，他们相亲相爱
No, wait, they love each other.
他们刚抵达时，确实是在互斗
They were at war when they arrived
但他们都讨厌火鸡，所以和解了
but they united over their hatred of turkeys.
他们相亲相爱，更爱教训火鸡
And what they love even more than each other is kicking turkey butt.
各位
Gentlemen.
又到了享用大餐的时候
成功了，走吧，山查兹
It's working! Come on, Sanchez
我们去把变形光束关掉
let's power down the humanizer ray.
我们是站在哪一边的？
Whose side are we on?
不知道，但为了学费做得够多了
I don't know, but we've done enough to pay for college.
－我们就快到了　－抱歉
- Look, we're almost there. - Sorry.
该由我负责带来惊喜了
My turn for a surprise.
天啊，他真的很喜欢从暗处登场
Damn, this guy loves arriving from the shadows.
你们是无法打败这群古代战士的
Look around, you can't beat our ancient warriors.
是吗？火鸡一直都在对抗掠食者
Can't I? My kind has always dealt with predators.
所以火鸡才会在树上睡觉
That's why we sleep in trees.
所以野生火鸡才会飞
And that's why, in the wild, we fly.
现在轮到你选择了
Now, you must choose.
看你要对付我还是阻止那武器
Fight me, or stop that weapon
把全美火鸡变成新的种族
from turning all of America's turkeys into a new master race.
你这蠢蛋，我们有三个人
You dumb dipshit, there's three of us
其中两个是太空人
and two of us are spacemen.
他们当然会去拯救美国
Obviously, they're going to save America
把纪念碑带回来
and bring that monument home.
而我会负责教训你
And I'm gonna kick your ass.
对了，山查兹？我赦免你
Oh, and Sanchez? You got your pardon.
闭嘴，莫蒂，我们走
Shut up, Morty! Come on!
－来吧，婊子　－没问题
- Let's go, bitch. - So be it.
火鸡人说的是真的吗？
Is it true what Turkey Man said?
火鸡会在树上睡觉吗？
That turkeys sleep in trees?
谁在乎，莫蒂？先关闭这武器
Who the hell cares, Morty? Let's just deactivate this shit.
计算中，锁定全美火鸡
Calibrating... Targeting all American turkeys.
天啊，竟然还有配音？
Oh my god, they gave it a voice?
配给谁听？这里是太空
Who is this for? We're in space.
天啊，瑞克，给他们听的吧？
Jeez, Rick... I guess them?
莫蒂，这要小心使用
Morty, use this carefully.
把变形核心打开，剪断蓝色电线
Crack the humanizer core and cut the blue wire.
听到没有？蓝色电线
You hear me? Blue wire!
什么？干吗不直接炸掉？
Why don't we just blow it up?
这是纪念碑，蠢蛋
It's a national monument, fucknut!
我们才刚被赦免
We just got pardoned.
你明年还想再重来一次吗？
You really wanna do this again next year?
你忘了一件事，火鸡人
You forgot something, Turkey Man.
即使你骗过了其他人
No matter what you got people to believe...
倒影池紧急关阀扳手
我还是真正的总统
I'm still the goddamn President.
你也忘了，我当上总统一天
And you forget, in the one day I've had your job...
就学到了十倍多的事
I've learned ten times as much.
倒影池备用紧急关阀扳手
－是我小看你了　－不会有下次
- I've underestimated you. - For the last time.
瑞克，这些颜色太相近了
Rick, they're not exactly primary colors!
蓝绿色可以吗？
Are we cool with like, turquoise?
有没有搞错，莫蒂？快点剪断
Are you kidding me, Morty? Just cut the damn thing!
靠，干
Oh, shit! Oh, fuck!
已锁定目标，启动武器
Targets acquired. Activating weapon.
靠
Oh, shit!
古迹已遭摧毁
Heritage destroyed.
莫蒂
Morty!
该死，我只交代你一件事而已
Goddamnit, you had one job!
我打败你了
I beat you!
看着我，你这死火鸡
Look at me, you turkey ass bitch.
等等，你干吗…这是许愿骨吗？
Wait, why are you... Is that a wishbone?
我希望能爆炸
I wish to explode.
－柏林围墙倒了　－这叫PS
- The Berlin Wall has come down. - It's called the PlayStation.
－《莎翁情史》获胜　－PS2
- The winner is Shakespeare In Love. - PlayStation 2.
卡崔娜飓风席卷路易斯安那州
Hurricane Katrina slams Louisiana.
－PS3　－有请魔力红
- PlayStation 3! - This is Maroon 5.
－PS4　－小熊队获胜
- PlayStation 4! - The Cubbies win!
我想要PS5
I want a PlayStation 5.
我不确定什么时候该拉你起来
I wasn't sure when to pull you out.
我猜你应该在经历人生跑马灯
I assumed you were running through your whole life.
没错，我的人生真精彩
Yes. And what a life it was.
各位，感谢你们再次拯救美国
Gentleman, thank you once again for saving this nation.
你背叛了你的人民
我不会讲你们的语言
I don't speak Googa.
中情局只有教我讲启动指令
The CIA only taught me your activation phrase.
但我如果会讲
But if I could say anything
我会请你们再给美国一次机会
I'd say, give America one more chance.
我从铁血战士那里拿到的
天啊，他们要打起来了，是真的
Oh my god, they're gonna fight, they're really gonna fight.
他们相亲相爱
They love each other!
－真感人　－百看不厌
- Never gets old. - I'll never get tired of that.
所以那些外星人发现美国之后
So, after those aliens discovered America...
他们就进入长眠了
They went into hibernation.
把科技交给我们，领导自由世界
Leaving us the technology we use to lead the free world.
还有蓄奴之类的事
That, and also to do stuff like slavery.
我一直以为我们很特别
I always thought we were... more special than that.
我们发明了一切，做了一切
Like we invented everything and did everything
所以我们才拥有一切
and that's why we own everything.
我现在不知道该作何感想
Now, I-I don't know what to feel.
心怀感恩，莫蒂，心怀感恩
Feel thankful, Morty. Feel thankful.
我知道，宝贝
I know, baby.
库普，要买哪一种早餐麦片？
Coop, honey, should we get Lucky Charms or Kibble Bibbitz?
你知道我们都买不起
You know we can't afford either.
宝贝，总统明明欠你人情
Baby, the President owes you.
你救了他一命
You saved him!
我们的保险预算被删减不能怪他
Ain't his fault our insurance got cut.
他们得生产飞弹
They gotta build missiles.
好吧，你可以抱一下杰克吗？
Fine, just... Can y'all hold Jakey for a second?
－他在干吗？　－他好像在觅食
- What the hell's he doing? - I think he's foraging.
这疯子以为自己是火鸡
Crazy bastard thinks he's a turkey.
我拒绝帮他出健保费用
Well, I refuse to pay for this man's healthcare.